[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "Did he do that to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "You'll to have to ask him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "Why are you reluctant to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "Because we have a show we're doing and it just -- I just don't want to say any incriminating things that will go to make it harder to kind of make peace.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "What was your reaction today when he finally resigned?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "It's pretty sad, because obviously he's an intelligent guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Were you surprised by the tone of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "I was surprised that he did it, frankly, to begin with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "Andrew Breitbart, I mean, do you feel vindicated today and do you have any sympathy for Anthony Weiner?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Yes, I do feel vindicated.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andrew Breitbart", "Anthony Weiner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "How do they best deal with this kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Well, there's several questions there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "Why is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "No, you don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "I mean, Andrew, if you had the same information right now -- and for all I know, you may well do -- on one of your own, a Republican, would you have gone after him with the same enthusiasm?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", ":", "CC", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "I'm not sure about the same enthusiasm, but I probably would have gone after him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andrew"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNPS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "And how much damage has it caused, if any?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "I think it has caused damage to the Democrats because in these three weeks, they were really thinking they had a little roll going on Medicare, spending and other issues, taxes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Do I think it's a good idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$200"]}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "$", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "Will you quiet down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "I want my $200.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Tatum, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I'm well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "What do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Like I've always thought you were part of our family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Do you have an overwhelming sense of relief -- both of you, do you think, that at least you manage to get back to somewhere, even if it's not perfect yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "IN", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "How did you feel when he asked you over for Father's Day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "'NEAL: I felt like I would be there for him because it's Father's Day and a day our show launches.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Have you watched it together yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "When you see that, do you wish sometime you had never been pushed into that world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "I don't really think about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Do you still watch it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Oh, yes, with my daughter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "About him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Let's focus on you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["98 percent"]}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "How much of the drugs played a part in the down side of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "'NEAL: I would say 98 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "How did you get them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "They were round.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "And what was the drug?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "First pot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Did he do that to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "You'll have to ask him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Why are you reluctant to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Because we have a show we're doing and it just -- I just don't want to say incriminating things that are going to make it harder to kind of make peace and have healing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "The one when you felt most ashamed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Obviously, like you showed, the arrest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "How did you get into heroin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Through a friend, a person after my divorce.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Do you still call them friend?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "And what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "I feel good about myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "How can this be the crazy Tatum O'Neal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Thank you for saying that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tatum O'Neal"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Do you think you're winning the battle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "I know I'm winning the battle.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "How long have you been clean now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "I've been sober for a year now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Are you proud of yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "Like beyond.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "So how could I not be proud?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "You should be proud.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", ":", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "First, what's your view of Weiner-Gate and (INAUDIBLE), really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", ":", "NNP", ":", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "First, it is really sad, because he was a really -- kind of an ambitious -- really ambitious, up and coming congressman, who wanted to be mayor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Do you recognize that kind of self-destruct button?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "What's the best way for any addict to try and deal with it once this has all been blown up like it has?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "RP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "There are so many different ways now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "What did you find was the best way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "For me, a 12 step program worked for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Did it save your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I know it is saving my life a day at a time, for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "How do you physically feel these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Do you miss drugs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Not even a little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Are you surprised at that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "I'm grateful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "You did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Did you ever get mad at her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "And I was looking at her pictures and thinking, gosh, how I am a going to compete?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", ",", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "One of the most beautiful women in the world, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Did you have any real relationship with her for a long time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Just that one that I write about in my book, where I went to talk to her while she knew she was sick in her apartment, and got to kind of talk to her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Was she sorry to you for what had happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "Do you think she was the love of your dad's life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "'NEAL: Well, I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Is this true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Well, if you know my dad, and you'll get to meet him, you'll sort of see that he is just always joking and stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "The word awkward could have been invented for that moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "Is he basically just an incurable romantic, do you think, your dad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "Totally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "He loves women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "You're so right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Do you know how old I was when I married him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "Twenty two.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "``", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "''", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "So do you think I had like the full idea of what I was doing in my life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "This was a guy smashing rackets and shouting \"you cannot be serious\".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "CD", "VBN", "NNS", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "How do you get on these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "We get on as well as a divorced couple who have three grown kids can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Do you talk regularly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 692, "question": "Do you talk to your ex-wife regularly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "Every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "Six years ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "Maybe two.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "Two years ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 717, "question": "Whose decision was it to end the marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 718, "answer": "Mine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "How did he take that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Not well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 725, "question": "What's your love life like these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 726, "answer": "Oh, I don't have any love life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "Zero?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "Zero.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "Are you looking for a man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "No, I'm really not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "What kind of man do you think now you ought to be with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "Maybe a gentle, smart, loving person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 740, "question": "Would you like to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 743, "question": "Wouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 744, "answer": "Yes, I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]